<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, ImageLabActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Image Playground</string>
    
    <string name="about_text">Image Playground 1.0\nCopyright 2012 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.\nhttp://code.google.com/p/image-playground\n\nThe script you enter in the text field will be called once for each pixel in the camera image. The script should return an output pixel value created from the gray or rgb functions described below.\n\nThese variables will be preinitialized:\ny: pixel brightness from 0 to 255\nr: red component from 0 to 255\ng: green component from 0 to 255\nb: blue component from 0 to 255\nrow: row number of current pixel, where 0 is the top\ncol: column number of current pixel, where 0 is the left\nwidth: width of the image in pixels\nheight: height of the image in pixels\n\nScripts can use standard Java arithmetic and bitwise operators, and can create new variables by assigning them to values. (All variables are integer type). The following functions are available:\nabs(x): absolute value of x\nmin(x,y): smaller of x and y\nmax(x,y): larger of x and y\nclamp(x,a,b): if x is less than a, returns a. If x is greater than b, returns b. Otherwise, returns x itself.\nifgt(x,y,a,b): if x is greater than y, returns a, otherwise returns b.\nbrightness(row,col): brightness (0-255) of image at row and column\nrandom(x): random integer between 0 and x-1\n\ngray(x): gray color with the given brightness\nrgb(r,g,b): color with the given red, green, and blue components\n\nThis software uses ANTLR 3, under the terms of the following license:\nANTLR 3 License\n\n[The BSD License]\nCopyright (c) 2010 Terence Parr\nAll rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n  - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n  - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n  - Neither the name of the author nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>
    <string name="noImagesFound">You have not saved any pictures yet.</string>

    <string name="deleteImageButtonLabel">Delete Picture</string>
    <string name="shareImageButtonLabel">Share Picture</string>
    <string name="exitViewImageButtonLabel">Return</string>
</resources>